‎NETFLIX アニメシリーズ
‎（デイビッド･マルティネス）
‎俺にインストールしてくれ
It's high time I chromed up.
Get the fuck outta here.
‎（リパードク）冗談だろ？
‎売るって話じゃなかったか？
I already gave you the quote to sell.
Not here to sell.
‎売らない　自分でつけたいんだ
I'm here to install.
‎（リパードク）やめとけ
Listen. That's military grade.
‎そいつは ただでさえ
‎合う合わないが激しい
You either got the build
to handle it or you don't.
‎そのうえ ガチの軍用だ
‎ガキが耐えられる‎代物(しろもん)‎じゃねえよ
And choom, you don't got it.
Spoken like a ripper
who cares about his clients.
‎カネさえ払えば
‎あんたの知ったことじゃないだろ
Hah! Snarky for a kid
who can't even afford me.
‎ハハッ カネなんか… んん
‎持ってねえだろうが
‎ハア… 分かったよ
Fuck you.
Hold on.
‎ちょっと待て
‎取引といかねえか？
Fuck it, man. I'll bite.
‎インストールはしてやる
I'll chip you up.
But when you come crying to yank it off…
‎その代わり 外したくなった時も
'cause it's poaching your brain,
I get the Sandy for free.
‎お前がくたばった時も
‎タダで俺が頂く
So, ready to rip?
‎いい話だろう？
‎うぐっ　うっ うっ…
‎うっ　ぐううううっ…
♪～
～♪
‎（ＡＩ教師）‎ラヴァーブル氏は
‎ＥＵの関税ポリシーを盾に
At the convention, Lavabre attempted
to persuade Arasaka by using the…
‎（ＡＩ教師）‎アラサカ社へ
‎圧力をかけようとしましたが…
Martinez, David.
Your tardiness has been recorded.
‎デイビッド･マルティネス君
‎大変 残念ですが遅刻になります
Get a load of this guy…
‎（カツオ･タナカ）おい 授業中だぞ
‎正気… がはっ！
Is he serio--
‎うっ クッ…
We're at school you gonk!
‎学校だっつってんだろ！
‎カメラあんだぞ バカなの…
There are cameras. Have you lost your--
‎うおーっ！
Afraid of getting caught?
‎記録に残るか？
'Cause I sure ain't.
‎俺には関係ねえな ほら
Come on.
‎クッ…
‎うい
Well?
‎（力み）
‎ホワーチョチョチョチョ…
‎（インプラント発動音）
‎チョチョッ　チョチョッ
‎チョッ
‎ホワーチョチョチョ…
Ow… That hurt…
‎だっ イテー！
Ow… What did you do?!
‎（カツオ）痛い 痛い 痛いっ
‎何だ クソッ！
What kind of implant is that?
You broke my nose!
‎どんなクローム 入れやがった
‎鼻が折れちゃったじゃないか
You're done for!
‎お前は おしまいだぞ
‎オヤジはアラサカの重役なんだ
My father's an Arasaka exec!
On the Academy's board!
‎アカデミーの理事もしてるから
‎お前を退学にするのなんて簡単だ
Do you know how easy it'd be
to have you expelled?
‎自分で辞めなくても
‎退学するハメに…
Like I give a shit.
‎（デイビッド）‎知るかよ クソ野郎
‎プッ… プッハ！
‎ハハハハッ アハハハハ…
‎（インプラント発動音）
‎（通行人）ん？
‎ハア…
Is he serio--
‎（カツオ）‎正気… がはっ！
‎ホワーチョチョチョ…
‎ぐはっ！
‎オヤジはアラサカの重役なんだ
My father's an Arasaka exec!
On the Academy's board!
‎アカデミーの理事もしてるから
‎お前を退学にするのなんて簡単だ
Do you know how easy it'd be
to have you expelled?
‎（ホロ通信：タナカ）
‎マーカス 教えてくれ
Marcus, why am I being shown footage
of my own son being assaulted?
‎なぜ息子が殴られる不愉快な映像を
‎見せられなきゃならんのかね？
This student is David Martinez,
17 years old, from Santo Domingo.
‎（マーカス）こ‎の生徒は
‎デイビッド･マルティネス 17歳
‎サントドミンゴ出身
He is a top student at the Academy,
‎成績は優秀ですが
‎先日 違法デバイスにより
‎アカデミーのシステムを破壊
but he was found using a bootleg wreath
that corrupted the Academy's hardware.
He has no father and his mother was
recently killed in a traffic accident.
‎父親はおらず母親は事故により死亡
‎現在 多額の負債を抱えており…
He owes a considerable amount of debt--
‎（タナカ）‎何の関係がある？
How is this relevant?
Notice his movements…
‎（マーカス）‎彼の異常な動き
He has the Sandevistan that James Norris
had at the time of this death.
‎このインプラントは
‎ジェームス･ノリス元中尉の
‎サンデヴィスタンに
‎間違いありません
‎（タナカ）
‎サイバーサイコシス化して
The case that was filed
as a cyberpsychotic incident.
‎処理した件だな？
Yes, sir.
‎（マーカス）
‎はい　歴戦の軍人でさえ
Yet, unlike the soldier, this student
displays no side effects from the implant.
‎耐えられなかった
‎インプラントですが
‎彼には副作用が見られません
His tolerance for cybernetics could make
him a prime candidate to test the product.
‎並外れた耐性があると推測され
‎例のプロダクトを試す よい人材に
‎なりえる可能性があります
‎（タナカ）‎なるほど　今 彼は？
‎（マーカス）‎即刻 退学処分に
I see. And where is he now?
He was expelled, sir.
Summon him.
‎（タナカ）‎呼び戻せ
‎何なら学費を支援してやってもいい
Lure him with the promise of
financial aid if you must.
‎（マーカス）
‎ご子息への暴力については？
And what of your son?
‎（タナカ）‎“社の利益は
‎すべてにおいて優先される”
As my heir, it's high time he learned…
‎私のせがれは分かっているさ
what it means to serve
the company's best interests.
‎（ホロコール着信音）
‎（校長）‎マルティネス君
‎規則に基づいた退学手続きが
‎自動で行われました
‎が タナカ君の親御さん…
‎（通信切断音）
I'm so fucked.
‎（デイビッド）終わったな～ 俺
‎（洗濯機の作動音）
‎（デイビッド）ハア…
‎（洗濯機の終了音）
Wash cycle complete…
‎（洗濯機ＡＩ）
‎洗濯が完了しました　洗濯が…
‎（男のいびき）
‎ハア…
‎（男の子）おーい 来いよ！
‎（男たちのあえぎ声）
‎（警察官）
‎やってらんないよ　安月給でさあ
‎ん？
‎（ルーシー）え？
‎（デイビッド）あ…
‎（ルーシー）ちょっと来な
‎（デイビッド）えっ あっ ちょ…
Come with me.
The hell is your problem?
‎どういうつもり？
What?
‎何が？
You're messing with my work.
‎私の仕事を邪魔したわ
Work? Looked more like a picksocket to me.
‎いや おとなしく
‎盗ませるやつがいるかよ
You some kinda badge?
‎チラチラ 私を見てたでしょ
Can't believe you're a petty thief…
‎（デイビッド）
‎まさか泥棒だったとは
‎うっ う…
‎（ルーシー）
‎フウ… どっかで会った？
Do I know you?
No… not really. Just--
‎いや た… たぶん は… 初めて
‎（ダンッ！）
‎（電子音）
Ooh, you're in trouble.
‎あ～あ こんなもんつけちゃって
Huh?
‎え？
Really? A Sandevistan?
Not an off-the-rack model, either.
‎ガキがサンデヴィスタン？
‎それも既製品じゃないわね
I won't press you.
This is Night City after all…
‎別に詮索はしないわ
‎それがナイトシティでしょ？
Crazy idea. How about we work together?
‎その代わり私の仕事を手伝わない？
What, stealing?
‎（デイビッド）泥棒を？
I only steal from Arasaka suits.
‎（ルーシー）
‎私が狙うのはアラサカのやつだけ
What about me then? I look corpo to you?
‎（デイビッド）
‎じゃあ俺は コーポに見えたの？
My scan picked up an ID
from Arasaka Academy.
‎スキャンしたら
‎アラサカアカデミーのＩＤ登録がね
But you're right,
you definitely don't look the type.
‎まっ 言われてみりゃ
‎コーポのガキには見えないか
‎（デイビッド）
‎もう辞めたよ あんなとこ
I dropped out.
Oh? A bad boy.
‎ふーん　問題児なんだ
‎（デイビッド）
‎狙うのはコーポだけだね？
It's just 'Saka you target?
‎（ルーシー）フッ 乗ってきたわね
You in?
Gonna break poor momma's heart, y'know.
‎賢く育ててくれた親に感謝なさい
‎ひっ！
Lesson number one.
‎（ルーシー）あんたマジで隙だらけ
Less judgment, more awareness.
‎レクチャーのしがいがあるわ
Yeah, yeah. So, what's my cut?
‎それで 俺の取り分は？
We'll split the haul 80-20.
‎私が８　あんたが２
Fuck that. Don't you need my Sandevistan?
‎はあ？　ふざけてる？
‎俺のサンデヴィスタンが
‎頼りなんだろ
‎盗(と)‎ったチップをさばくのもこっち
But I'm the one pushing
the klepped shards.
Plus, now I have a trainee to supervise.
‎それに あんたの授業料もあるわ
Trainee…?
‎授業料ね
I'm actually tight on eddies right now.
Can't we do 60-40?
‎実は俺もカネが要るんだ
‎せめて‎６：４(ろくよん)‎にならない？
‎７：３(ななさん)
70-30. And I'll pay you
the second the job's done.
‎仕事が終わったら その場で
‎取り分 払うってのでどう？
Fine.
‎分かった
It's a deal.
‎決まりね
‎ルーシーよ
Call me Lucy.
‎デイビッドだ
David.
‎（ホロ通信：デイビッド）
‎つながった　聞こえる？
‎（ルーシー）‎聞こえてる
‎（デイビッド）
‎こっちも聞こえてる
‎ターゲットは？
‎（ルーシー）‎３時の方向
‎（デイビッド）‎了解
‎（ルーシー）‎侵入するわ
‎オーケー 準備して　いい？
‎３ ２ １　行くよ
‎（デイビッド）‎成功
‎（ルーシー）
‎初心者コースよ　次からが本番
‎（デイビッド）‎よっしゃ
‎（ルーシー）
‎おしゃべり中の‎ＯＬ(オーエル)‎はノーガード
‎ＢＤ(ビーディー)‎中はおいしいカモ
‎（デイビッド）‎簡単すぎ
‎チュートリアルは もういいだろ
‎（ルーシー）‎オーケー
‎じゃあ いよいよモンスター狩りよ
‎（デイビッド）‎オー…　げっ！
‎う… コーポじゃないよね？
‎（ルーシー）
‎アラサカの用心棒よ　３ ２…
‎（デイビッド）
‎えっ ちょちょちょ… ぐっ…
‎（ルーシー）‎やるじゃない
‎モンスタークリアね　次で降りるわ
‎（デイビッド）‎ハア… 了解
So? How did I do?
‎（デイビッド）
‎どう？　うまくやれただろ
I'd say you're well worth the 20%.
‎（ルーシー）
‎まあ ２割分の仕事はできたかな
It's 30!
‎（デイビッド）３割だろ
‎（ルーシー）フフッ 冗談よ
Kidding.
Keep it rolling on another car?
‎（デイビッド）
‎乗り換えて またやる？
Maybe a different line.
By now, someone's probably noticed.
‎路線も替えるわ
‎そろそろ気付いたやつもいるでしょ
（鼻血が滴る音）
We should keep the risk to a minimum…
（デイビッド）
あ… ああ…
‎リスクは最小限に…
How bad?
‎（ルーシー）どうなの？
‎（救急隊員）初心者がよくやるの
Rookie mistake.
Hasn't taken any precautions
since installing that implant.
‎負荷の高いインプラントを
‎慣らしもせずに使ったんでしょ
Which immunosuppressant is he on?
‎（救急隊員）抑制剤は何を？
He insured?
‎彼 保険は？
No clue. Doesn't look like he would be.
‎知らないわ
‎入ってるようには見えないけど
Any family or guardian? Anyone I can call?
‎（救急隊員）誰か呼べる家族は？
‎緊急連絡先とか
Dunno. Parents, I guess.
‎（ルーシー）だから知らない
‎親ぐらいはいるんじゃない？
‎アカデミーの生徒だったって
He used to go to the Academy.
‎（救急隊員）
‎アラサカ？　だから こんな…
Arasaka? No wonder he could afford this.
Hold on…
‎ちょっと失礼
‎（イスがきしむ音）
Hey. How ya feeling?
‎どう？　現状への感想は？
I'm gonna be sick…
‎気持ち悪い
Which immunosuppressant do you take?
‎（ルーシー）抑制剤は何使ってる？
‎（デイビッド）何それ
Immuno… what?
‎ハハハハッ　ウソでしょ？
‎イカれてるわ
Wow, man…
You're psycho.
‎ヘヘッ
‎（クラクション）
‎（車の加速音）
‎ちょっと 通り過ぎて…
Hey, we passed the…
‎（カチャ！）
Oh my.
‎（ルーシー）あら～
Listen, choom, the kid's got
an implant that'll fetch a nice price.
‎この子の入れてるインプラント
‎すごく高価なものなの
Just sit back, relax and--
‎黙っておとなしくしていれば…
What? You cut a deal
with the Scavengers or something?
‎何？　スカベンジャーにでも
‎売り渡すわけ？
Sit back or I'll take your chrome, too.
‎嫌なら
‎あんたのインプラントも頂く
Sorry, David.
‎デイビッド
‎やっぱり私が８で あんたが２だわ
Looks like your cut's down to 20.
‎（デイビッド）ん… えっ？
‎（ガタン！）
‎（２人）うっ…
‎う… わっ！
‎フフン
‎（デイビッド）んんんー！
‎フウ～ッ！　ハハッ 最高ー！
Let's go!
‎（ルーシーの笑い声）
‎フッ
‎（デイビッド）ぐぐぐ…
‎（ルーシー）あれ？
Whoops.
‎ちょっと～ 大丈夫？
Hey, not dying, are ya?
‎リ… リパー
Doc…
Huh?
‎ん？
Doc's clinic… Please… take…
‎リパーのとこに連れて…
‎（ルーシー）ハア～
David, buddy…
‎（リパードク）よお デイビッド
‎ひどいザマだな 平気か？
You look like shit.
Thanks…
‎（デイビッド）いや…
‎（リパードク）
‎ハハッ 何回 使った？
How many times you use it?
Six… No, eight?
‎（デイビッド）６… ８回ぐらい？
Jesus Henry Christ!
‎（リパードク）おいおい バカか？
‎大人でも発狂する回数だぞ
A grown-ass man
couldn't take that punishment.
‎何ともなかったんだけど
‎急に鼻血が出て…
I was fine…
But then my nose popped a cork.
‎（ルーシー）こいつ抑制剤のこと
‎知らなかったみたいだけど
This gonk didn't know about
immunosuppressants.
‎（リパードク）
‎ああ 必要ないと思ってな
Didn't see the need.
Of course you didn't.
Just sell him the meds.
‎（ルーシー）
‎あきれたやつね　早く薬を出して
Shit off the shelf's not gonna cut it.
It'll cost ya.
‎（リパードク）
‎普通のじゃ効かねえからな
‎ちっと高いぜ　カネはあんのか？
You good for it?
You charging me?
‎カネ 取るのか…
Fucking right I am!
Ain't running no charity.
‎（リパードク）そりゃ当然だろ
‎サービスは手術代までだ
‎（ルーシー）これでどう？
‎（チップを置く音）
How much'll these buy?
‎（リパードク）フッ ２日分だな
‎（袋を置く音）
Two days' worth.
That's it?
‎（ルーシー）それだけ？
Plenty of other rippers out there.
‎（リパードク）
‎嫌なら街の医者に行きな
Of course, that might land you
back with the Scavs.
‎またスカベンジャーに
‎売り飛ばされんのがオチだろうがな
‎ハハハーッ！
Greedy bastard…
‎（デイビッド）悪徳リパーめ
‎（ドアの開閉音）
You really don't want it gone?
‎（リパードク）
‎まだ外すつもりはないようだな
‎（デイビッド）ない
Nope.
Still can't believe it…
Eight times in one goddamn day.
‎（リパードク）
‎そいつを１日に８度も起動させて
‎平気だとは信じられん
‎お前が鈍感なだけか
You're either a total masochist or…
Listen. Don't use it more than
two times a day. Three max.
‎だが使い過ぎはやめとけ
‎せいぜい１日に２度
‎多くて３度までだな
Even if your body can take it,
that egghead of yours can't.
‎仮に体が受け入れても頭は別だ
Your brain's gonna get scrambled.
‎こいつは確実にお前さんの精神を
‎むしばむだろうよ
A single implant
could make me a cyberpsycho?
‎サイバーサイコシスに
‎なるってこと？
Never heard anything like that before.
‎インプラント１つで？
‎そんなの聞いたことない
Goes to show you…
‎それくらいヤバい代物ってことさ
just how dangerous that thing is.
‎フッ
All done?
‎もういいの？
Yeah.
‎ああ
Guess that's a wrap for today.
‎今日はもう 仕事はやめね
I can keep going.
‎やれるよ 俺
‎ダメよ
No way, I'm not babysitting a cyberpsycho.
‎サイバーサイコの面倒見るのは
‎ごめんだわ
Only use the Sandevistan
when you really need to.
‎サンデヴィスタンは
‎いざという時だけ使えばいいわ
‎ほかにも やりようはある
Lots of other ways to churn out eds.
Still willing to work with me
after all that?
‎まだ俺と組む気あるんだ…
Think I'd let you go
without being paid back first?
‎今日の分 返してもらわないとね
‎あ～
Well, good. I need the eddies.
‎（デイビッド）
‎俺もやりたい　カネが要るんだ
That's the spirit.
‎（ルーシー）決まりね
‎（デイビッド）
‎やっぱり もうひと稼ぎしない？
Sure you're not up for more tonight?
I'm kinda lagging on rent.
‎大家に家を追い出されそうでさ
No more today. Quit asking.
‎（ルーシー）
‎今日は もうダメ　諦めな
‎（デイビッド）だよな
Okay…
Come with me.
‎（ルーシー）来て
I knew you wanted to!
‎（デイビッド）
‎おっ そうこなくっちゃ
Not work-related.
‎（ルーシー）仕事じゃないわよ
‎（デイビッド）え？
Huh?
Right here.
‎（ルーシー）ここよ
‎（デイビッド）えっと… 独り？
You, uh… live alone?
Yeah?
‎（ルーシー）そうだけど
‎（デイビッド）ふーん
Huh.
‎もしかして緊張してる？
Wait, are you nervous?
‎いや
No.
Your first time?
‎初めてとか？
No.
‎いや
‎フフフッ
Hey, fuck off!
‎してないって！
Take a seat.
‎（ルーシー）座って
‎ビールしかないからビールね
I've only got beer. You drink?
Uh, yeah.
‎（デイビッド）あ… うん　乾杯
Cheers.
‎（のどが鳴る音）
‎うっ…
‎（せき込み）
‎（ルーシー）ちょっと
‎何？　まさか酒も初めてなの？
Seriously? You've never drunk before?
No, I have. It's just…
‎（デイビッド）酒はいいんだけど
‎（ルーシー）んー？
I don't like carbonated drinks or smokes.
‎炭酸とタバコは苦手なんだ
‎フッ そんなやついるかな？
Do people like that really exist?
‎ホントだって
I'm not lying.
‎（ルーシー）
‎ダッサ　あんた服もダサい
Sure you aren't.
And what's up with that getup anyway?
‎（足音）
Take it off.
‎（ルーシー）脱いで
‎（デイビッド）えっ なんで？
What? Why?
Just do it. Come on.
‎（ルーシー）いいから貸しなよ
‎（デイビッド）お… おい
H-Hey!
‎（操作音）
‎（デイビッド）あっ ちょ…
‎勝手に描くなよ
Don't mess with that…
‎ん？
Edgerunners?
エッジランナーズ？
It's another word for cyberpunk.
（ルーシー）
サイバーパンクの別名よ
It's who you wanna be, right?
なるんでしょ あんた
‎フッ ‎ＪＫ(ジェーケー)‎のエッジランナーズは
‎めっちゃ見てた
I'm actually a fan of JK's
"EDGERUNNERS" series.
‎フフフッ そっち？
You serious?
‎フッ そっちこそ
‎あのダサいポスター 部屋に貼る？
Look who's talking.
What's up with that tacky poster?
You got a problem?
‎悪い？
Uh… no problem.
‎（デイビッド）
‎え… あ いや 悪くはないけど
Just always whacked me how those ads
make it seem like some kind of paradise.
‎よく広告で この世の楽園みたいに
‎宣伝してるけどさ
I mean, lots of peeps died trying to
turn that dumb rock into something useful.
‎月開発のために
‎どれだけ人が死んでるか知ってる？
Sounds more like a prison than paradise.
‎楽園っていうより地獄だよ
Sounds like someone did their homework.
‎（ルーシー）詳しいのね
The Academy teaches you things
they don't show in the ads.
‎（デイビッド）アカデミーじゃ
‎広告で言わないことも
‎教えられるからね
As expected of a preppy Academy boy.
‎（ルーシー）さすが
‎アラサカアカデミーのお坊ちゃん
It's not like that.
‎（デイビッド）そんなんじゃない
Isn't it? Never caught a pleb
attending a 'Saka school.
‎（ルーシー）通ってるだけでも
‎十分 お坊ちゃんだわ
It's not!
‎違う！
‎プハッ
My mom and I, we weren't well off.
‎うち 父親もカネもなくてさ
The Academy normally
wouldn't have taken me.
‎アカデミーなんて
‎行けるような家じゃなかった
But my mom had to work real
damn hard to keep me in.
‎でも母さんは
‎俺をアカデミーに行かせたいって
‎相当 無理してて…
You wanna know the kicker though?
I knew from day one that I'd never belong.
‎けど 行って すぐに分かった
‎こんなやつらに
‎なじめるわけないって
Then why did you stick around for so long?
‎（ルーシー）それが分かって
‎なんですぐに辞めなかったの？
‎（デイビッド）無理でしょ
Good fucking question. Guess it's 'cause
Mom wanted me to get a 'Saka job,
‎アカデミーに行って
‎アラサカに就職して
‎高い所で仕事して…
climb the corporate ladder…
‎それが母さんの望みっていうか
That was her wish… Or dream, I guess.
‎夢ってやつ だったから…
That's why.
‎それって他人の夢じゃん
That's not your dream, though.
Not my dream?
‎他人？
Well, yeah. You and your mom
are two different people.
‎（ルーシー）
‎親子って別々の人間でしょ
Why should you need to work for her dream?
‎あんた人の夢のために生きてるの？
There's nothing wrong with that.
‎（デイビッド）
‎それって ダメなことなのかな？
You have to find your own dream.
‎（ルーシー）
‎夢は他人のものじゃないわ
Sounds like you've found yours.
‎（デイビッド）
‎自分には夢があるって口ぶりだね
You're joking.
‎マジなの？
‎（ルーシー）
‎あんたは地獄っていうけどさ
You called it a prison, but to me,
this city is a whole lot worse.
‎私にとっては ここが地獄
Here?
‎（デイビッド）ここが？
‎（ルーシー）
‎私は遠いとこへ行きたいんだ
I just wanna go away as far as possible.
‎いいもの見せてあげる
Lemme show you something.
‎ん？
Whoa! Check the resolution on this!
‎（デイビッド）
‎うおおっ すっげえ解像度
I can feel the fucking sun!
‎太陽 熱っ！
It connects through your personal link
to let you feel the sun's heat.
‎パーソナルリンク経由で
‎太陽光の熱を感じさせてるの
Of course, you'd burn to a crisp
if it was the real temperature,
‎リアルな設定だと
‎熱すぎてヤバいから
‎人が感じて大丈夫なくらいには
‎セーブしてるわ
so I made sure to tweak it down.
Want me to change it back?
‎オフにする？
No, this is fun!
‎面白いから これでいい
‎アッハハ 何その格好
You look ridiculous!
‎んっ よっ　ハハッ
‎うっ フハハハッ おっと
Pretty cool, huh?
‎（ルーシー）いいでしょ？
‎（デイビッド）これ最高！
This is amazing!
Isn't it?
‎（ルーシー）でしょ？
‎（デイビッド）アハハッ ハハッ
Over here.
‎こっち来て
‎あ…
‎あっ　おわっ！
‎（ルーシー）フフフッ
‎（デイビッド）フッ
‎（エンジン音）
‎（ルーシー）フフフッ
‎ヘヘヘヘッ
‎（せき込み）
‎ん？
‎（ルーシー）フフフッ アハハハッ
‎（デイビッド）フン！
First time I've ever shown anyone this.
‎（ルーシー）
‎誰かとやるの 初めてだ
Oh… really?
‎（デイビッド）そう… なんだ
So, like… why me?
‎えっと… なんで見せてくれたの？
No idea. Guess it just felt right.
‎（ルーシー）なんでだろ？
‎あんたには見せてもいいかなって
‎（デイビッド）ふーん
You know…
‎私たち
I think we'd make a good team.
‎いいコンビになりそうじゃない？
Yeah…
‎（デイビッド）そうだね…
‎あ…
‎（ホロ通信：メイン）
‎エッジを越えちまったな 小僧
Huh?
‎へ？
‎うわっ　い… でっ！
Hate to break it to ya,
but that implant belongs to me.
‎（メイン）
‎小僧　悪いがそいつは 俺んだ
‎返してもらうぜ
I'll be taking it back now.
‎うっ　え…
‎あ～
‎うがっ
♪～
～♪